Kionta Thomas

2156 NE 7th Avenue Apt A Portland, OR 97212 (940) 206-6992 Kionta_kionta@yahoo.com

Profile

Generous experience in many areas of customer service, problem solving, and cash handling. Proven ability to come up with creative solutions to difficult problems has earned my employers tremendous respect, and customer loyalty. Earned a reputation for exceeding expectations in all positions held, and known for being tremendously loyal. Customer Service is priority one.

Employment History

Trainer

Others Helping Others, Lake Dallas, Texas

May 2006 - Apr 2011

OHO provides effective, comprehensive, and timely services to any and all persons with developmental, physical, and emotional disabilities.

- ♦ Worked with the disabled to obtain life skills and helped them to become a bigger part of society.
- ♦ Screened properties for clients, ensuring that their housing would best meet their individual needs.
- ◆ Taught and led workshops to clients that would improve their abilities to assemble products and complete projects independently.
- Responsible for assisting clients in transportation for their social and daily needs.

Customer Service Specialist

Banana Republic, Grapevine, Texas

Sept 2010 – May 2011

Banana Republic is a specialty retailer offering clothing, accessories and personal care products for men, women, children and babies. Their presence is felt around the world with more than 3,100 company-operated stores and 175 franchise stores.

- Created a welcoming and clean environment for customers.
- ♦ Maintained and organized stock.
- Performed cash handling and register operations.
- Managed fitting rooms and assisted customers with all their outfitting and accessorizing needs.

Front Desk Administrator

Extended Stay Hotels, Lewisville, Texas

Nov 2009 - Oct 2010

This company has emerged as the category leader with the largest distribution of extended stay properties in the United States. Extended Stay Hotels owns and operates nearly 700 hotels across the United States and in Canada.

- Responsible for reservations and checking in and out our guests.
- ♦ Acted as Concierge for our guests, assisting them with all personal requests.
- Fixed any problems in individual rooms, and ensured our guests had a great experience.

Backstock Lead

Tommy Hilfiger, Grapevine, Texas

Aug 2005 – Feb 2006

As one of the world's leading premium lifestyle brands, Tommy Hilfiger delivers superior styling, quality and value to consumers worldwide.

- First Shipment Supervisor at this location. Organized entire stock room.
- Responsible for increasing sales on sales floor.

Education

2006

Lewisville High School, Lewisville, Texas

Diploma

♦ Graduated in Top 15% of class, among 695 students